<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on ฅ՞•ﻌ•՞ฅ Bear’s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on ฅ՞•ﻌ•՞ฅ Bear’s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hugo&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Website: &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;https://gohugo.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Written in Go, Hugo is an open-source static site generator available under the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gohugoio/hugo/blob/master/LICENSE&#34;&gt;Apache Licence 2.0.&lt;/a&gt; Hugo supports TOML, YAML, and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files, and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification, and support for Sass SCSS workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/yuin/goldmark&#34;&gt;https://github.com/yuin/goldmark&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma&#34;&gt;https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop&#34;&gt;https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/spf13/cobra&#34;&gt;https://github.com/spf13/cobra&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/spf13/viper&#34;&gt;https://github.com/spf13/viper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hugo is ideal for blogs, corporate websites, creative portfolios, online magazines, single-page applications, or even a website with thousands of pages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bear/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;bear&#34;&gt;Bear&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Website: &lt;a href=&#34;https://bearblog.dev&#34;&gt;https://bearblog.dev&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a website obesity crisis. Bloated websites are full of scripts, ads, and trackers slowing your readers down every time they try to read your well-crafted content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bear is all you need to build a fantastic and optimized site or blog. It works perfectly on &lt;strong&gt;any&lt;/strong&gt; viewing device. All you need to focus on is writing good content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bear makes it simple to publish content online and grow an audience while keeping pages tiny, fast, and &lt;strong&gt;optimized for search engines.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Augmentation in Programming: Antirez&#39;s Insights</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/llm-augmentation-in-programming-antirezs-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/llm-augmentation-in-programming-antirezs-insights/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;llm-augmentation-in-programming-antirezs-insights&#34;&gt;LLM Augmentation in Programming: Antirez&amp;rsquo;s Insights&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Salvatore Sanfilippo, better known as antirez, has once again shared invaluable perspectives on the evolving landscape of software development, this time focusing on the practical integration of Large Language Models (LLMs) into the programmer&amp;rsquo;s workflow. His latest post offers a pragmatic guide to leveraging advanced LLMs like Gemini 2.5 PRO and Claude Opus 4, moving beyond the hype to focus on tangible benefits and essential human-AI collaboration practices.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fading Community: Lessons from Maple Story&#39;s Decline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-fading-community-lessons-from-maple-storys-decline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-fading-community-lessons-from-maple-storys-decline/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-fading-echoes-of-community-why-were-stepping-away-from-social-games&#34;&gt;The Fading Echoes of Community: Why We&amp;rsquo;re Stepping Away from Social Games&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our digital landscape is undergoing a subtle but significant shift: individuals are increasingly choosing to step away from social games. What was once a vibrant hub of interaction is now, for many, a source of frustration or a pastime left behind. The journey of Maple Story, a once wildly popular game, offers a compelling microcosm of these broader trends.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Modern Maple World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-modern-maple-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-modern-maple-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-fading-echoes-of-community-why-were-stepping-away-from-social-games&#34;&gt;The Fading Echoes of Community: Why We&amp;rsquo;re Stepping Away from Social Games&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Look around our digital landscape today, and a subtle but significant shift is occurring. More and more individuals are actively choosing to step away from the once-enthralling world of social games. What was once a vibrant hub of interaction, competition, and camaraderie is now, for many, a source of frustration or simply a pastime left behind. To understand this phenomenon, let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the life cycle of a once wildly popular game: Maple Story. Its journey offers a compelling microcosm of the broader trends we&amp;rsquo;re witnessing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
