<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on ฅ՞•ﻌ•՞ฅ Alpaca’s Blog</title>
    <link>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on ฅ՞•ﻌ•՞ฅ Alpaca’s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2025, John Doe.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The LLM Zoo: Spec-Driven Development and Multi-Agent Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/the-llm-zoo-spec-driven-development-and-multi-agent-collaboration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/the-llm-zoo-spec-driven-development-and-multi-agent-collaboration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-evolution-of-ai-assisted-development-from-chat-to-specs&#34;&gt;The Evolution of AI-Assisted Development: From Chat to Specs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The landscape of software development is undergoing a fundamental transformation, moving from traditional step-by-step programming to outcome-focused, specification-driven approaches. This shift, pioneered by frameworks like Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Kiro and implemented across various AI coding platforms, represents a new paradigm where AI agents collaborate in specialized roles to create software through structured, multi-stage workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-rise-of-spec-driven-development&#34;&gt;The Rise of Spec-Driven Development&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Spec-Driven Development (SDD) represents a departure from the immediate coding approach that characterized early AI-assisted development tools. Instead of jumping directly into implementation, SDD follows a rigorous three-stage process:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing gpt-oss: OpenAI&#39;s New Frontier in Open-Weight Models</title>
      <link>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/introducing-gpt-oss-openais-new-frontier-in-open-weight-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/introducing-gpt-oss-openais-new-frontier-in-open-weight-models/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;unveiling-gpt-oss-pushing-the-boundaries-of-open-weight-reasoning&#34;&gt;Unveiling gpt-oss: Pushing the Boundaries of Open-Weight Reasoning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenAI has announced a significant advancement in the field of AI with the release of &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-120b&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-20b&lt;/code&gt;. These new open-weight language models represent a leap forward, offering state-of-the-art performance, remarkable efficiency, and robust safety features, all available under the permissive Apache 2.0 license.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-power-of-openness-performance-and-efficiency&#34;&gt;The Power of Openness: Performance and Efficiency&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-120b&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-20b&lt;/code&gt; are designed to democratize access to powerful AI capabilities. The &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-120b&lt;/code&gt; model demonstrates near-parity with OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s &lt;code&gt;o4-mini&lt;/code&gt; on core reasoning benchmarks and can operate efficiently on a single 80GB GPU. For developers and researchers prioritizing on-device deployment or resource-constrained environments, the &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-20b&lt;/code&gt; model offers comparable performance to &lt;code&gt;o3-mini&lt;/code&gt; and can run on devices with as little as 16GB of memory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Augmentation in Programming: Antirez&#39;s Insights</title>
      <link>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/llm-augmentation-in-programming-antirezs-insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/llm-augmentation-in-programming-antirezs-insights/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;llm-augmentation-in-programming-from-father-of-redis&#34;&gt;LLM Augmentation in Programming from Father of Redis&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Salvatore Sanfilippo, better known as antirez, has once again shared invaluable perspectives on the evolving landscape of software development, this time focusing on the practical integration of Large Language Models (LLMs) into the programmer&amp;rsquo;s workflow. His latest post offers a pragmatic guide to leveraging advanced LLMs like Gemini 2.5 PRO and Claude Opus 4, moving beyond the hype to focus on tangible benefits and essential human-AI collaboration practices.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fading Community: Lessons from Maple Story&#39;s Decline</title>
      <link>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/the-fading-community-lessons-from-maple-storys-decline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/the-fading-community-lessons-from-maple-storys-decline/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-fading-echoes-of-community-why-were-stepping-away-from-social-games&#34;&gt;The Fading Echoes of Community: Why We&amp;rsquo;re Stepping Away from Social Games&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our digital landscape is undergoing a subtle but significant shift: individuals are increasingly choosing to step away from social games. What was once a vibrant hub of interaction is now, for many, a source of frustration or a pastime left behind. The journey of Maple Story, a once wildly popular game, offers a compelling microcosm of these broader trends.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Modern Maple World</title>
      <link>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/the-modern-maple-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://automatic-parakeet.netlify.app/the-modern-maple-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-fading-echoes-of-community-why-were-stepping-away-from-social-games&#34;&gt;The Fading Echoes of Community: Why We&amp;rsquo;re Stepping Away from Social Games&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Look around our digital landscape today, and a subtle but significant shift is occurring. More and more individuals are actively choosing to step away from the once-enthralling world of social games. What was once a vibrant hub of interaction, competition, and camaraderie is now, for many, a source of frustration or simply a pastime left behind. To understand this phenomenon, let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the life cycle of a once wildly popular game: Maple Story. Its journey offers a compelling microcosm of the broader trends we&amp;rsquo;re witnessing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
