<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on ฅ՞•ﻌ•՞ฅ Bear’s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on ฅ՞•ﻌ•՞ฅ Bear’s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introducing gpt-oss: OpenAI&#39;s New Frontier in Open-Weight Models</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/introducing-gpt-oss-openais-new-frontier-in-open-weight-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/introducing-gpt-oss-openais-new-frontier-in-open-weight-models/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;unveiling-gpt-oss-pushing-the-boundaries-of-open-weight-reasoning&#34;&gt;Unveiling &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss&lt;/code&gt;: Pushing the Boundaries of Open-Weight Reasoning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenAI has announced a significant advancement in the field of AI with the release of &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-120b&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-20b&lt;/code&gt;. These new open-weight language models represent a leap forward, offering state-of-the-art performance, remarkable efficiency, and robust safety features, all available under the permissive Apache 2.0 license.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-power-of-openness-performance-and-efficiency&#34;&gt;The Power of Openness: Performance and Efficiency&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-120b&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-20b&lt;/code&gt; are designed to democratize access to powerful AI capabilities. The &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-120b&lt;/code&gt; model demonstrates near-parity with OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s &lt;code&gt;o4-mini&lt;/code&gt; on core reasoning benchmarks and can operate efficiently on a single 80GB GPU. For developers and researchers prioritizing on-device deployment or resource-constrained environments, the &lt;code&gt;gpt-oss-20b&lt;/code&gt; model offers comparable performance to &lt;code&gt;o3-mini&lt;/code&gt; and can run on devices with as little as 16GB of memory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fading Community: Lessons from Maple Story&#39;s Decline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-fading-community-lessons-from-maple-storys-decline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-fading-community-lessons-from-maple-storys-decline/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-fading-echoes-of-community-why-were-stepping-away-from-social-games&#34;&gt;The Fading Echoes of Community: Why We&amp;rsquo;re Stepping Away from Social Games&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our digital landscape is undergoing a subtle but significant shift: individuals are increasingly choosing to step away from social games. What was once a vibrant hub of interaction is now, for many, a source of frustration or a pastime left behind. The journey of Maple Story, a once wildly popular game, offers a compelling microcosm of these broader trends.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Modern Maple World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-modern-maple-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-modern-maple-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-fading-echoes-of-community-why-were-stepping-away-from-social-games&#34;&gt;The Fading Echoes of Community: Why We&amp;rsquo;re Stepping Away from Social Games&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Look around our digital landscape today, and a subtle but significant shift is occurring. More and more individuals are actively choosing to step away from the once-enthralling world of social games. What was once a vibrant hub of interaction, competition, and camaraderie is now, for many, a source of frustration or simply a pastime left behind. To understand this phenomenon, let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the life cycle of a once wildly popular game: Maple Story. Its journey offers a compelling microcosm of the broader trends we&amp;rsquo;re witnessing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
